[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 33]
Have you ever thought
maybe
there is another way to break the curse
other than to cleave the Four Seasons Monument?
Yes, there is
in the legend.
But we tried it before.
It didn't work at all,
did it?
That's because
I only inherited the immortal energy of Immortal Ze Shui.
I didn't inherit her resentment.
No matter how I try to forgive,
I just can't do it.
But just now,
the memory of the Brahma tree has told me
as long as the inheritor
becomes the Demon Queen,
she will have the right to forgive the Demons
and break the curse for ten thousand years.
Do you remember
that time
I tried to break the curse?
Demon King,
I'm afraid...
I can't break the curse.
Maybe
someone thinks
I'm not qualified.
But if
I become the Demon Queen,
what I carry
♫The begonia is red, but every promise makes it more withered♫
is the hope of the whole Demons.
♫It blooms alone, but the wind and rain are more violent♫
You mean
♫Plants are not human beings, and ruthless fruits are planted♫
you're willing to marry me and become the Demon Queen?
But
you and Fu have sacrificed too much.
♫How can you forget the innocence and ignorance when we first met?♫
As long as that lunatic who is locked up
would be able to
♫The butterfly emerges from the chrysalis, but it is difficult to fly to the sky♫
to be free
and those people who would die without water
♫The butterfly's wings were broken, and the dream fell without a trace♫
can be saved.
♫Because of their greed for the warmth of fire, they lost each other♫
Have you ever
thought about Fu's feelings?
He has committed so many sins.
♫There is a period of youth, and he is waiting for the spring breeze in the coming year♫
Has he ever thought about my feelings?
After I become the Demon Queen
and break the curse,
Fu won't risk his life
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
and it will end
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
all these disputes.
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
Compared to these,
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
our love hardly matters.
What about you?
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
Do you dare to do it?
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
Let me out!
I want to see Luo Ning!
Brother.
Fu.
How is Luo Ning?
I recalled
what she heard when she hid her breath.
She must hate
♫The butterfly emerges from the chrysalis, but it is difficult to fly to the sky♫
every word I said.
If I don't explain to her,
she might never
want to see me again.
♫The butterfly's wings were broken, and the dream fell without a trace♫
What can you tell her?
♫Because of their greed for the warmth of fire, they lost each other♫
Tell her that you never did those things.
Or you never make
♫There is a period of youth, and he is waiting for the spring breeze in the coming year♫
those plans?
I know.
What I did
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
is all wrong in her eyes.
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
Is everything I did wrong
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
in your eyes?
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
Fu,
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
I've been indulging you too much these years.
♫I'm willing to spread my wings♫
♫And don't fight the fate♫
♫It's a good moment to share the world with you♫
Brother.
Fu,
I'm sorry.
I hope when you come out,
the curse of the Aquatic Demons
would be broken.
You won't need to be bothered anymore
and you can live well.
You two
♫How many times do we have to reincarnate♫
are willing to
♫Before we meet again in the next life?♫
see me be imprisoned here for 100 years.
♫Suffer all grief and long hate♫
♫Reversed right and wrong dreams♫
♫I exiled my thousand-year-old body♫
♫Waiting for the ashes to slowly burn in the heart♫
♫Wait until the end of life to see the begonia turn red again♫
You're back.
Brother.
When did you get here?
I've been here all day.
I just want to see
when you will come back.
I went out for a while.
Something happened.
I was injured.
Luckily, I was saved.
You were badly injured.
Who hurt you?
The one who hurt me...
The one who hurt me
has been punished by the person who saved me.
What are you talking about?
All right, that's not important.
Well,
if the person who saved me
is talented and kind,
can I marry him?
Luo Ning,
I just want you to find
a kind and decent man.
As long as he's not a demon,
I will ask no more.
It looks like
Luo Ning is determined to marry the Demon King.
But I really don't know
how you did it.
That day,
I knew that Wan Sui would go to the Demon Palace.
So I asked you
to show up in front of him.
Bai Feng.
Wan Sui would definitely
-spread it. -They are totally different.
How could they be brothers?
Master.
Who?
Then I told
Luo Ning
about the Demon King and Immortal Ze Shui.
I watched her grow up
and I know her best.
She will definitely investigate it herself.
In this way,
Fu
will be punished by He Na.
If you do this,
how will he help you?
He is locked up by He Na.
Fu is arrogant
and difficult to control.
But I need someone
who can help me cleave the Four Seasons Monument.
He has the bloodline of the Demon King
and he is the best candidate.
Before that,
I must
curb his temper.
Go to the Demon Palace and keep an eye on him
and find out his movements.
Then
come back and report to me.
Yes.
Fu,
I'm not afraid you won't listen to me.
In the past few months,
the Four Seasons Monument has been in trouble too frequently.
Could it be the spy hiding in Immortal Palace
doing something bad?
This time,
I ask you here
to tell you something.
Please go ahead.
Xie Lingqi hid Wu Shiwei's immortal energy
in the Bone Melting Pool.
Besides, Wu Shiwei has been trapped in Yin-yang Cave
for a thousand years.
She is like a walking dead.
We must investigate her immortal energy.
Xie Lingqi resists
the inspection and purification.
Isn't that suspicious?
I think
Xie Lingqi
is probably still doing evil deeds for the evil.
He is the spy.
It’s easy to prove his innocence.
General Xie,
all you need to do is to hand over Wu Shiwei's immortal energy.
Hand it over?
Why?
That immortal energy
is the only thing Shiwei left.
You are asking me to hand it over?
Why don't you kill me?
I believe Xie Lingqi is innocent.
The Four Seasons Monument has been in trouble several times.
It might be the evil spirit
in the immortal energy.
But
do you have any solid evidence?
Ge,
a leopard can't change
its spots.
Don't be indecisive.
Xie Lingqi can't do
this damage.
Immortal Master,
I've checked
the damage to the Four Seasons Monument.
It has nothing to do with him.
General Xie is innocent.
The evil is very cunning.
He makes us suspect each other and makes people panic.
That's what he wants to see.
Don't panic.
Yes.
Shiwei,
I will become the senior
in your heart,
right?
I know you didn't do it.
But I need you to pretend to be imprisoned
to help me find
the spy hiding in the Immortal Palace.
I will protect the Immortal Palace.
Immortal,
someone has been coming in and going out the Xiyin Mountain recently.
Maybe the spy
is taking action again.
The situation is getting more dangerous.
Liu Shao,
every progress you make
is our chip to succeed.
What do you think?
Am I good?
Not bad.
What do you mean by that? Praise me.
You've improved a lot.
Last time I saw Luo Ning,
she seemed to have something on her mind.
Should I go check on her?
Okay.
Your brother said you have something on your mind.
I came to see you.
Nothing.
Really?
Liu Shao.
Do you know?
I saw it with my own eyes in the Demon Palace that
the people of the Aquatic Demons
died in front of me.
It was so miserable.
I don't want to see
it happen again.
I can end all of this.
I'm the inheritor of the Immortal Ze Shui's immortal energy.
I can break this curse.
So,
I want to marry He Na.
Luo Ning.
When did you know
you're the inheritor of Immortal Ze Shui?
The moment I found out that
I can summon
and activate Bone-Corroding Harp.
Since young,
you asked me to copy scriptures
and forbid me to touch anything related to the demonic world.
I guess
that's the reason.
Since you know it,
you should know
what happened between the Demon King and Ze Shui ten thousand years ago.
I will never agree to
this marriage.
But this marriage is not a loss to me.
Brother,
you are the only one who loves me.
But it's different now.
Now there's He Na.
He won't interfere with my life.
My life
will be more free
and more noble.
Isn't that good?
Luo Ning,
the curse of the Aquatic Demons has nothing to do with you.
The Three Realms shouldn't be your responsibility.
You should find someone you love
to spend your life together.
I can't.
What did you say?
I said
I can't find him.
The person I used to like
has been kicked to hell by me.
I even closed
his coffin tightly.
He will never come out again.
I will never
let him hurt
the people I love the most.
You mean...
Fu?
Did Fu do something to you?
Brother, stop mentioning him.
I just want you to know that
I will become the Demon Queen
and break the curse for the Aquatic Demons.
I promise
I will live a happy life.
Please help me.
No.
I can't let you sacrifice your happiness
for a curse.
So what?
If you don't agree,
I'll marry him anyway.
If you lock me up,
I'll get rid of Ze Shui's immortal energy
and drown myself in this pond.
You...
Immortal Luo Ge.
Immortal Master Wanwu said something happened to the Four Seasons Monument.
Please go over.
♫The remaining flowers in the mirror reflect the moon in the water♫
♫We can't live up to such a good time♫
♫Recalling the unforgettable glance at the beginning♫
Luo Ning,
are you really going to sacrifice your life
♫I realized that it was a thousand years ago♫
for a curse?
♫Is this bad luck, or good luck?♫
This curse of thousands of years
♫He said that responsibility and love are difficult to balance♫
has driven so many people crazy.
♫He had no choice but to leave me♫
I'm just
♫The past has passed, so do not linger♫
one of them.
♫My love for you is still so strong♫
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
♫Life is like a grain of sand♫
♫It burns the fire in my heart♫
♫I want to burn myself to hear you say you have never changed♫
In this world
everything
have to choose their own fate.
I thought
I was a carefree fairy in the Xiyin Mountain.
I don't need to think about anything.
But in the end,
we have to move forward
and make our own choices.
♫Why have you been so far away from me every time♫
I hope everything I do
♫For billions of years♫
can remove his inner demon
♫Can I use your hands to warm up the world again?♫
and let him live again.
♫A few hasty nights♫
Do you think
the person in front of you
♫Too many intertwined oaths and lies♫
is not the one who made you laugh
and played with you?
I am
♫Have shattered my dreams♫
the real Fu now.
♫Who would like to take a broken willow branch and watch the moon alone in the blue sky♫
Since this is caused by Ze Shui,
let me end it.
Your Majesty,
could the curse of the Demons
be broken this time?
Yes.
I'm going to the Immortal Palace.
Will Immortal Luo Ge
agree?
Whether he agrees or not,
I have to
discuss it with him in advance.
And I have to say goodbye
to Liu Shao.
Miss Liu Shao.
My name is Kho.
It's your demon.
My demon?
Kho?
Don't hit my demon!
This is my demon.
How can I hand him over?
No.
Your demon?
You're so beautiful and kind.
You don't talk much
every time you lie.
And you will tilt your head to the left like this.
People could see you through at a glance.
If you don't fight for
some things,
you will never get it.
From now on,
I will try my best
to get what I want,
no matter it's for the survival of my people
or the people I care about.
You mean Fu?
And you.
My Demon Palace still lacks a Demon Queen.
He Na...
I...
Just kidding.
Anyway, remember
you are not alone.
At least in the Demon Palace,
I will be by your side.
From now on,
I'm no longer
your demon.
Fairy Luo Ning,
I will go to Palace Chonghua
to propose the marriage to your brother.
You are quite decisive
this time.
I'm sorry.
This is only about the Aquatic Demons,
but it involves your happiness.
It's unfair
and even despicable to you.
The curse of the Aquatic Demons
was originally caused by Immortal Ze Shui.
Since
I inherited the immortal energy of Immortal Ze Shui,
I should
end it.
Besides,
the Aquatic Demons
have been punished for ten thousand years.
I shouldn't let this hatred continue.
You and Fu
should have a different life.
Fu.
Fu is too obsessed with hatred.
He deserved it.
And as his brother,
I didn't take good care of him.
He treats you...
Since I've decided to let go,
I won't regret it.
All my decisions
have nothing to do with him.
This marriage is
just to break the curse.
I am the Demon King.
It's my duty.
But you were the happiest fairy in the Xiyin Mountain.
After the curse is broken,
it will just be the title
of Demon Queen.
I can still be
the happiest fairy.
Besides, I think
you won't stop me from going anywhere freely.
Demon Palace and Immortal Palace.
You can go anywhere you want.
No matter where you go,
whether you want to
keep the title of Demon Queen,
in the heart of me and the Aquatic Demons,
Fairy Luo Ning
will be always the most respectable person.
We will never
forget it.
Luo Ning wants to marry you.
Is that true?
You know it?
Luo Ning
told me.
Are you blaming me for being selfish and having an ulterior motive
to marry Luo Ning?
I know you've been thinking about your people
and your responsibility as the Demon King.
But...
It's the Demon King's responsibility,
not He Na's.
He Na is a boy in white who can't lie.
He would do anything
for his friends.
What about him?
I once thought
to follow my heart.
But seeing the girl I like
having a better future,
I feel relieved.
I can't just think about the girl I like.
Now,
I can only be the Demon King.
Since I've taken the honor of the Demon King,
I'm destined to take the responsibility of the Demon King.
There are
countless people behind me
who have been longing for sunlight and land.
There are thousands of people who yearn for a happy family
like me.
If I can exchange thousands of people's happiness
with my unhappy marriage,
I think it's worth it.
He Na.
Liu Shao.
Thank you.
♫I want to get close but I can't see clearly♫
♫Who arranged this rain?♫
♫I want to avoid but I meet you again♫
I can't give the pendant
to you.
♫I can't help but stay with you♫
♫The stars call the morning sky♫
♫May you feel relieved♫
♫I long for a hug♫
Thank you.
Thank you for letting me meet you.
♫Can I not just listen?♫
♫I want to find our way through destiny♫
♫I want to throw away the memory in exchange for you to come back♫
♫Raise the glass to reincarnate the world♫
♫I'll wait for your response with no regrets♫
♫I'll find the promised home for you♫
♫My heart aches and I will say yes again♫
♫When will we separate?♫
♫Please don't tell us our ending in advance♫
Wow.
Demon King spent a lot.
Of course.
Otherwise, how can he marry our fairy?
What do you think is inside?
It must be something you've never seen.
Take back what you brought.
Or we'll not be friends.
Luo Ge,
I sincerely want to marry Luo Ning.
The person you care about is not Luo Ning.
Maybe not now.
But in the future,
the person I care about
is Luo Ning.
Luo Ge,
please believe me.
I will protect her
and treat her as my life.
I will try my best to make her happy for the rest of her life.
Her happiness
is to spend her life
with her beloved one.
There shouldn't be any schemes.
He Na,
I always respect you for being a gentleman in the demons.
But what you are doing now is not gentlemanly.
You think I'm scheming against her?
Am I wrong?
Luo Ning is a kind girl.
She has been trying to break the curse of your people.
I don't care about that.
I don't even mind helping you out.
But this is not the reason to sacrifice my sister's life happiness.
If there is any other possibility,
I would rather fill myself in
to block the curse
and don't want to implicate others.
Then fill yourself in.
Don't implicate my sister.
He Na.
I don't mind you counting me in
when you fill yourself in.
But please let my sister go.
Luo Ge,
why don't you ask Luo Ning
about her thoughts?
You've been strict with Luo Ning
because you're worried that she'll follow Immortal Ze Shui's path.
It's all my fault.
If I could protect her better,
I might be able to avoid her
getting on this path.
This wouldn't have happened.
Actually, I've talked to He Na.
He's totally different from Fu.
He won't be impulsive and cruel
just like the Demon King ten thousand years ago.
I think he can take good care of Luo Ning.
Don't worry too much about that.
I know He Na's character too.
I just hope
she can be happy forever.
Luo Ge,
are you really not going to attend Luo Ning's wedding?
That's the Demon King in White,
not the Demon King.
What if
Luo Ning cries?
What will she do?
It's the most important day for Luo Ning
and she can't see her brother.
Poor thing.
Just copy the Meditation Spell.
Don't do anything evil.
Do good deeds.
Get rid of all evil ideas
and eliminate the sins.
Didn't you just promise me
to kill those who hurt me?
Now,
it's just a hundred years of imprisonment.
Even if I was wrong,
even if I failed you,
are you really so cruel?
A hundred years.
Can you bear not to see me for a hundred years?
Luo Ge,
I'm sorry.
You can be sorry to me,
but you can't let Luo Ning down.
My only wish
is the peace of the Three Realms
and the happiness of the people
even if I have to sacrifice my life.
But I never thought
my sister would do the same one day.
I just want her to be happy
in this life.
Okay.
I can't wait.
The Demon Palace and Immortal Palace
are all under my control.
Soon,
I'll be the master of the Three Realms.
[Happiness]
Mr. Tai,
how is Fu these days?
General Fu
has been quiet lately.
He made a mistake
and he should be punished.
It's a good thing
for him to cultivate himself.
But I feel guilty
for marrying Luo Ning.
You did it
for the Aquatic Demons.
I'll explain to him
after the curse is broken.
I hope our people
will get rid of the fate of living in the water
and use our race name again.
Melody race.
I hope you can
lead us to land
and revive the Melody race.
Luo Ning,
I did as you said.
I copied scriptures.
I copied many scriptures.
Can you stop being angry?
Mr. Tai.
General Fu.
Where is my brother?
His Majesty is busy,
so he sent me here
to see if you need anything.
Yes.
I want to see Luo Ning.
I can't decide on that.
You can show the scriptures
to her.
She will see me.
I will report it
to His Majesty.
Do you have to tell him about such a small matter?
Do you know
I may actually lose her?
I can feel
she's going to give me up.
What?
You don't want to?
What happened?
If there's nothing else, General Fu,
I'll leave now.
Is my brother really going to give me up
and imprison me here for a hundred years?
General Fu,
His Majesty really loves you.
Mr. Tai,
I can't stay here for a hundred years.
No way!